A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 6, Accession 6 FA1188
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Board of Directors, Committees, and Members records, 1966-2006; 11
  - Mailing ("Red China Today"), 1970 February 27 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    "Red China Today," Supplement section, Kansas City Star, 1969 September 23, has been separated to box 50, but there is a copy of the paper in the file.
  - Program and Member Mailings, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 44-46)
    Mailing November 16-17, 1970: James C. Thompson, Jr., "Will the Nixon Administration Recognize Communist China?", November 20-23: Robert F. Byrnes, "When the Academic Door to Peking Opens", December 4: John R. Garson, "The American Trade Embargo of China."
  - Member Mailings, 1966-1974 (Box 4, Folder 47-50)
  - Member Mailings and Annual Members Meeting, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 51-58)
  - Member Mailings and Annual Members Meeting, 1979-1989 (Box 6, Folder 59-69)
  - Member Mailings and Annual Members Meeting, 1990-1999 (Box 7, Folder 70-78)
  - Member Mailings and Annual Members Meeting, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 79-81)
  - Board and Members Mailings and Annual Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 82-83)
  - Board and Members Mailings, 2005 January-February (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Executive Committee Meetings and Mailings, 1967-1972 (Box 10, Folder 103-107)
  - Executive Committee Meetings and Mailings, 1973-1981 (Box 11, Folder 108-116)
  - Executive Committee Meetings and Mailings, 1982-1994 (Box 12, Folder 117-126)
    Records for 1983 not found.
  - Executive Committee Meetings and Mailings, 1995-2003 (Box 13, Folder 127-134)
  - Board of Directors Membership Responses, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Board of Directors Annual Meeting Attendance (Responses), 1998 November 19-20 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Minutes Book, 1966 September 9-1976 May 21 (Box 32, Folder 287-291)
    Minutes of meetings of the Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and Membership Nominating Committee, plus Bylaws and Articles of Incorporation.
  - Minutes Book, 1966 September 9-1967 (Box 32, Folder 292)
    Minutes of meetings of the Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and Membership Nominating Committee, plus Bylaws and Articles of Incorporation. Arthur Rosen copy.
  - Minutes Book, 1968-1975 October 29 (Box 33, Folder 293-296)
    Minutes of meetings of the Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and Membership Nominating Committee. Arthur Rosen copy.
  - Program Summary and Proposals, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 297-298)
  - Program Expansion Proposal, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 299)
  - National Committee Brochures, 1966-1970 (Box 33, Folder 300)
    File of brochures on National Committee programs, membership, and events.
  - National Committee Financial Statements, 1967-1970 (Box 34, Folder 301)
  - Fundraising Letter, 1969 September 22 (Box 34, Folder 302)
    Thank-you letter to individual contributors to the 1969 Convocation on China, including offer of subscription to China Clearinghouse.
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1971 November-December, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 303)
    Procedures and accounting for mail distribution, telephone and photocopier usage, correspondence concerning reimbursement to contributor.
  - Requests for Information and Assistance, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 304)
    Includes proposal by National Wushu Association of American for documentary on Wushu in China.
  - Annual Members Dinner and Symposium, 1974 June 3-4 (Box 34, Folder 305)
    Budget and planning.
  - Annual Members Meeting, 1978 July 5 (Box 34, Folder 306)
    Planning and acceptances.
  - NCUSCR - Articles of Incorporation, 1974-1990 (Box 41, Folder 354)
  - NCUSCR - Public Charity Determination Letter, 1976-2006 (Box 41, Folder 355)
  - Separated Oversize Material (Box 50)
    Oversized material separated from Series 11, box 4, folder 43; and from Series 10, box 21, folder 194.
- Clippings and Reference, 1987-1989; 15
  The Clippings and Reference series in RG 6 contains press coverage of China in the period of the Tiananmen Square uprising. Contents notably include a set of the Foreign Broadcast Information Service Daily Report on China from May-October 1989.
  - Foreign Broadcast Information Service Daily Report China, 1989 May 30 - June 13 (Box 34, Folder 307-309)
  - Foreign Broadcast Information Service Daily Report China, 1989 June - July 25 (Box 35, Folder 310-314)
  - Foreign Broadcast Information Service Daily Report China, 1989 July 26 - September 15 (Box 36, Folder 315-320)
  - Foreign Broadcast Information Service Daily Report China, 1989 September 18 - October 6 (Box 37, Folder 321-323)
  - China Spring Digest, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 324)
    Volume 1, numbers 1 and 4 (1987), volume 2, number 1 (January-February 1988).
  - China Press Coverage (Beijing Digest), 1989 May-October (Box 37, Folder 325)
    Magazines relating to China in the summer of Tiananmen: Beijing Digest, 1989 May-October. Issues of the Far Eastern Economic Review from May - November 1989 and May 31, 1990, were discarded in processing and not retained in the file.
  - Free China Journal, 1989 May 25 - June 19 (Box 37, Folder 326)
    Coverage of China and Tiananmen protests.